#06 "The Tulip Lion"
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Noir Stardia  LP.2000
Skills [Great Sage] [Get Creative] [Editor] [Bestow]
Skills [LP Conversion] [Stone Bullet] [Discerning Eye]
Skills [Headache Immunity] [Pocket Dimension (Grade C)]
Skills [Improved Back Step] [Passive Defense]
Skills [Shoulder Rub] [Lucky Lecher]
Skills [Dungeon Elevator]
Noir Stardia  LP.1400
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Noir Stardia  LP.1200
Skills [Great Sage] [Get Creative] [Editor] [Bestow]
Skills [LP Conversion] [Stone Bullet] [Discerning Eye]
Skills [Headache Immunity] [Pocket Dimension (Grade C)]
Skills [Improved Back Step] [Passive Defense]
Skills [Shoulder Rub] [Lucky Lecher]
Skills [Dungeon Elevator] [Blinding Light]
Name:
Level:
Skills:
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Noir Stardia  LP.1200
Skills [Great Sage] [Get Creative] [Editor] [Bestow]
Skills [LP Conversion] [Stone Bullet] [Discerning Eye]
Skills [Headache Immunity] [Pocket Dimension (Grade C)]
Skills [Improved Back Step] [Passive Defense]
Skills [Shoulder Rub] [Lucky Lecher]
Skills [Dungeon Elevator] [Blinding Light] [Night Vision]
Noir Stardia  LP.1000
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Sextuple Zombie Lv.110
Skills [Contagious] [Undead]
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Zombie    Lv.170
Skills [Archery (Grade B)]
Skills [Dual-Wielded Daggers (Grade C)]
Skills [Sharp Ears] [Wind Strike]
Skills [Zombified]
Archery (Grade B)
Dual-Wielded Daggers (Grade C)
Sharp Ears
Hello
Why does he have
a tulip on his head?
[Zombified]
Needed to delete
Available LP.
Alice Theater
#07 "The Receptionist Ranking"
Illustration: Mitsumomo Mamu